800ceoread.com 2004-12-08

# 800CEOREAD.com

|  | 

**Information You Provide**  
There are a few activities on our site where the collection of personally identifiable information is necessary. Those activities include things like registering for a contest, making a purchase, or contacting us. When personally identifiable information is collected, you will know because you will have to fill out a form. For most activities, we collect only the most basic contact information. 

**Information Collected from You with Technology**  
800-CEO-READ collects some information about you using technology, so it may not be readily apparent to you that it is being collected. For instance, when you come to our site your IP address is collected so that we know where to send information you are requesting. An IP address is often associated with the place from which you enter the Internet like your ISP (Internet Service Provider), your company, or your university. This information is not personally identifiable. We don't combine this type of information with personally identifiable information. 

**Does 800-CEO-READ share information with companies or other organizations?**  
One of the most valuable assets of our business is you. We aren't in the business of selling information about our Guests. We do not release our information to any other companies or organizations. 

**Companies That Are Service Providers of 800-CEO-READ**  
Sometimes we hire companies to help us deliver products or services, like a shipping company that delivers a package. In those instances, we need to share your information with them. These companies are solely "Service Providers", and they are allowed to use the information only to deliver the product or service. 

**Organizations That Help Protect the Security and Safety of our Guests and our Sites**  
We will give out personal information as required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena; to enforce our Terms of Service, or to protect the safety and security of Guests and our sites. 

**How does 800-CEO-READ use the personally identifiable information that has been collected?**  
800-CEO-READ uses personally identifiable information in a limited number of ways. We use the information to complete transactions. We use information collected to notify you if you've won a contest. Information we collect is used to send you e-mail updates about our site, provided you have indicated your desire to receive such information. 

**What type of security does 800-CEO-READ provide?**  
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our guests is of utmost concern to us. 800-CEO-READ takes technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect all visitors' information. 

**Whom do I contact with questions or concerns about this privacy policy?**  
If you need further assistance, please contact us: 

**800-CEO-READ**  
219 North Milwaukee Street, 3rd Floor  
Milwaukee, Wisconsin 53202  

Phone: 800-236-7323  
Email: [Click to Email](mailto:info@800ceoread.com)   

---  

**Featured Title**

**[Purple Cow   
Collectable Milk Carton](http://www.1800ceoread.com/details.asp?productid=097030997X) **   

* * *

**Welcome to America's best supplier of business resources!

If you don't find what you're looking for on our site, please call us today at  
800-236-7323!

**

 **   
**  
  
_Book data provided by  
Copyright April 1995-2004, for personal non-commercial use only. All rights reserved._  
Privacy Policy
